http://www.joeshouse.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology
that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy
applies to the Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients Web site and governs data collection and usage.
By using the Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients website, you consent to the data practices described
in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail
address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients also
collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as
your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically
collected by Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients. This information can include: your IP address,
browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This
information is used by Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients for the operation of the service, to
maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use
of the Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information
or personally sensitive data through Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients public message boards,
this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients
does not read any of your private online communications.
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites
you choose to link to from Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients so that you can understand how those
Web sites collect, use and share your information. Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients is not responsible
for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients
and Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients collects and uses your personal information to operate the Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients
Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients also uses
your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services
available from Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients and its affiliates. Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients may also
contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services
or of potential new services that may be offered.
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business
partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases,
your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone
number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients
may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send
you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All
such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to
provide these services to Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients, and they are required to maintain
the confidentiality of your information.
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such
as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients, in order to determine what Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients services are
the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising
within Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested
in a particular subject area.
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice,
only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is
necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process
served on Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or
property of Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect
the personal safety of users of Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online
experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page
server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the
domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save
you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned
to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients pages, or
register with Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients site or services, a cookie helps Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients
to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process
of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses,
and so on. When you return to the same Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients Web site, the information
you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients
features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically
accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies
if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience
the interactive features of the Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients secures your personal information from unauthorized access,
use or disclosure. Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients secures the personally identifiable information
you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit
card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use
of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect
company and customer feedback. Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients encourages you to periodically
review this Statement to be informed of how Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients is protecting your
information.
Contact Information
Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy.
If you believe that Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients has not adhered to this Statement, please
contact Joe's House - a Lodging Guide for Cancer Patients at david.ulf@joeshouse.org.
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the
problem.
